Ordinary guy, extraordinary arsenal.
The Survivalist is a action, science fiction,
thriller film directed by Jon Keeyes.
A year and a half after the fall of civilization from a virus outbreak, a former FBI agent is forced to protect a young woman, who is immune
to the disease, from a dangerous gang hunting her led by a psychopath who believes he’s going to use her to save the world.
Ben, played by Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
Aaron Ramsey, played by John Malkovich.
Sarah, played by Ruby Modine.
Marley, played by Jenna Leigh Green.
Heath, played by Julian Sands.
Radio Operator (voice), played by Lori Petty.
The Survivalist is a 2021 American action thriller film directed by Jon Keeyes and
written by Matthew Rogers starring Jonathan Rhys Meyers and John Malkovich.
It is about woman who is thought to be immune to a pandemic who is fleeing from a
religious leader and his followers who think she could be a cure.
It was released in the United States on October 1, 2021, by Quiver Distribution.
The film explores themes of affectation, angry, aggressive, clinical, casual.
The tone is thought_provoking and intense.